shewrites.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy

**_Effective Date:   March 1, 2011_**

**PRIVACY PRACTICE STATEMENT AND POLICY**

She Writes, Inc. (“SHEWRITES”) believes that understanding what our customers want regarding collaborations, products, services and opportunities is very important and valuable. SHEWRITES is committed to protecting the privacy of users of our services.  The purpose of this privacy practice statement and policy is to inform you of the kinds of information we may gather about you when you register for and use our services or access our web site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose it to others.

SHEWRITES wants to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for you if you choose to become a user of our website (“Site”).  SHEWRITES has designed its Site with this belief in mind, and has created this Privacy Policy so that you can have easy access to SHEWRITES’ stated privacy practices.  At any time, however, SHEWRITES may change its privacy practices and policies, and we encourage you to return to this Privacy Practice Statement and Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) frequently to learn about our policies and practices concerning how we collect and treat confidential and personal information that you share with us by visiting and using our Site and services.  Changes in our policies and practices will be posted here and will be effective when posted.

SHEWRITES is the sole owner of the information it gathers on its Site.  SHEWRITES will only share your Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") with outside parties in ways that are described in this Policy from time to time, or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to legal requirements, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on SHEWRITES.

SHEWRITES adheres to the European Union Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information covered by the Privacy Policy from the European Union.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

All personal information ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. SHEWRITES may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of all changes in the Privacy Policy by posting these changes on the Privacy Policy linked to our Site at [](https://www.shewrites.com/)[https://www.shewrites.com](https://www.shewrites.com/).  If as the result of such changes you want to alter the ways in which SHEWRITES is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences."  You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to SHEWRITES, you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by SHEWRITES or by third parties, SHEWRITES will not change your preference in this regard without your consent. However, if SHEWRITES sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or SHEWRITES (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with another entity, you agree that SHEWRITES may provide to such entity Personal Information, including any PII, that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without obtaining your further consent. SHEWRITES will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on this Site to the extent that Personal Information or PII is transferred.

**Your California Privacy Rights** **:**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our members who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.  If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

She Writes, Inc.

60 State Street #3C

Brooklyn, NY 11201-6750

**What information does SHEWRITES collect on-line** **?**

When you visit SHEWRITES’ Site, SHEWRITES may ask you to provide information by filling out and submitting an online form.  This requested information may include your name, phone number(s), e-mail address, and mailing address.  For privacy purposes all information relating to our customers is stored in a highly secure server that is not accessible via the Internet and will not be shared with any third parties.  You can always choose whether or not to disclose any or all of the information requested; however, certain information may be required in order to be able to respond to your request.  If you do not want to disclose any requested information over the Site you may contact SHEWRITES’ at the address at the foot of this Policy to complete your registration or request information.

**Information we collect** ** **

We may elect to do one or more of the following with respect to the information we collect:

  * We collect the information you give us in order to provide you programs, products, services and opportunities (including but not limited to webinars, events, programs, conferences, lectures and training sessions), inform you about our programs, products, services and opportunities, and fulfill your orders and service requests.
  * We use cookies and other Internet technologies, including web beacons, to manage our Site and e-mail programs, to offer you personalized experiences, and to help us manage our Site.
  * When you access our Site, we use your IP address for internal purposes and to customize your browsing experience.  We also utilize your IP address for security purposes and to protect your information.
  * When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser (such as Mozilla’s “FIRFOX” or Microsoft’s “Internet Explorer”) automatically transmits some information to SHEWRITES every time you access content on one of our sites. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our site. All of this information may be collected by SHEWRITES and used to help improve our services or the offerings our members may make to you.

**What sort of information will SHEWRITES not collect?** ** **

The only information SHEWRITES may collect is information that you voluntarily provide to SHEWRITES, which may include your acceptance of “cookies” or web beacons or information that your computer automatically provides.

**Who collects personal information?**

Personal information on this Site is collected on behalf of SHEWRITES by SHEWRITES, who is responsible for this Site. SHEWRITES’ address is She Writes, Inc., 60 State Street #3C, Brooklyn, NY 11201-6750.

The Site contains links to other sites where personal information is or may be collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your Personal Information or PII will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site and not be this Privacy Policy. That site’s privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your Personal Information or PII and how it will be used.

**“Cookies” or Web Beacons — if SHEWRITES sends you cookies, what are they and how does SHEWRITES use them?   What are Web Beacons and how does SHEWRITES use them?**

Cookies are small pieces of text that store information specific to your browsing session with SHEWRITES.  A cookie does not contain code or any other malicious data.  We utilize this recurring information to customize your browser experience while you are utilizing SHEWRITES resources, and it ensures the proper credentials are being used to secure your information from unwanted viewers.  The majority of information SHEWRITES retrieves from your cookies is contained in “Session Cookies” and is not permanently stored or remembered.

A Web Beacon is an embedded object that is usually attached to an image or framing object.  In many cases, this embedded code pulls an image or other object from a third party site and is generally used in user tracking.  Web beacons help us measure the effectiveness of our Site and our advertising. For example, web beacons may count the number of individuals who visit our Site from a particular advertisement or who make a purchase from our Site after viewing a particular advertisement or posting, or they may tell us when a web page is viewed and provide a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Web beacons may also measure the effectiveness of our email campaigns by measuring click-throughs and the frequency that these emails are forwarded.

The information we or our contractors collect through web beacons may include some limited personal information.  They also allow us to recognize users by accessing our cookies. We may also combine the information that we collect through web beacons with other personal information we have collected from you. We use all of this information to better tailor our marketing to you and may use this information for other purposes, such as to enable a shopping cart, customize content on our Site and undertake internal research.

We may allow third parties to compile individual information or aggregated statistics from the use of web beacons on our Site or otherwise placed by us, to enable such third parties to determine the effectiveness of online marketing and to allow such third parties to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement results in an action on the advertiser's site. Aggregate information is anonymous and may include demographic and usage information. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with such third parties for this research.

SHEWRITES may hire other companies to place our banner ads on other websites. Such companies perform tracking and reporting activities on ads served and user reaction ("third-party advertisement servers"). They are not authorized by SHEWRITES to collect any information other than IP addresses and behaviors associated with those IP addresses on our behalf, and we do not give any personal information to them. Third-party advertisement servers are subject to and may have their own privacy policies.

SHEWRITES may allow other companies to display advertisements on certain pages of the Site or within the Products and Services. If you click on these advertisements these companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer which may allow them to display further advertisements to you. It is our policy to require these companies to provide accessible methods for you to disable these cookies. Should you have any complaints about the practices of any of these companies you should contact [privacy@shewrites.com](mailto:privacy@shewrites.com).

When you receive an email from SHEWRITES, we may track whether you opened that email and clicked on any links included in the email.

**How does SHEWRITES use the information it collects** **?**

SHEWRITES may use the information it collects to improve its Site, enhance SHEWRITES’ existing programs, product offerings, services, community, and to introduce new product offerings and services and opportunities (including but not limited to webinars, events, programs, conferences, lectures and training sessions).

**How we use personal information** **:**

SHEWRITES may elect to do one or more of the following:

  * We use personal information to deliver the services and support, or to carry out the transactions you have requested.
  * We use the information collected to send communications to you, such as product safety information, your transactions status (for example, order confirmations), information about products and services and opportunities (including but not limited to webinars, events, programs, conferences, lectures and training sessions) available from SHEWRITES and its corporate affiliates, promotional offers, and surveys.
  * We use the information to customize, analyze, and improve our products, services (including our Site), opportunities (including but not limited to webinars, events, programs, conferences, lectures and training sessions), technologies, communications and, relationship with you.
  * We use the information to enforce our conditions of sale, Site terms and/or separate contracts (if applicable) with you.
  * We use information to prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities.
  * We use information to generate notices regarding new products or services or opportunities (including but not limited to webinars, events, programs, conferences, lectures and training sessions).

**How does SHEWRITES use email** **?**

SHEWRITES encourages you to email SHEWRITES with your questions or comments.  SHEWRITES reads every email it receives.  If you request to have your email address added to our mailing list, SHEWRITES will periodically send new information to you.  If you want your email address removed from the list at any time, just instruct us to do so by email addressed to “remove.shewrites.com”, indicating in the subject line that you wish to be removed.  Please include your name and the email address you wish to have us remove so that we may identify the appropriate email address to be removed.

**What information may SHEWRITES share with others** **?**

SHEWRITES will not share, sell or trade email addresses, which are personal to you, and that are collected as part of a survey, with others.  Except to verify credit card information to complete your product/service/opportunity transaction, or in connection with an acquisition of SHEWRITES or its assets where an appropriate confidentiality agreement is in place, SHEWRITES will not use or release to others any credit card or financial information for any purpose.  For privacy purposes, all information relating to our customers is stored on a highly secure server that is not accessible via the Internet and will not be shared with any third parties.

However, if you respond to any solicitations (e.g., from writers, collaborators, publishers, etc.) or from advertisers, then we will have no control over how these third parties use your information. ** **

**Protecting personal information** ** **

We understand the importance of ensuring that your personal information is secure and protected.  We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect personal information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure.

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the Site or of the programs, products or services available on our Site or from our members is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available to you through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. In addition, your Registration Information resides on secure servers where only selected SHEWRITES’ personnel and contractors have access via administrative level passwords. SHEWRITES encrypts your personal information as it is transferred to SHEWRITES and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information. Unfortunately, although we have taken these steps, there is a possibility that a third party may, without our authorization, breach our security procedures and access such information.

It is your responsibility to keep your password and unique customer Id confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**Disclosing personal information** ** **

  * We share your personal information with corporate affiliates to carry out transactions you request or to make our business or that of our corporate affiliates more responsive to your needs.
  * We may share your personal information with business partners that help SHEWRITES carry out transactions you request or that help SHEWRITES to customize, analyze and/or improve our communications or relationship with you, and then only with business partners who share SHEWRITES' commitment to protecting your personal information.
  * We may disclose your personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, or other legal action as required by law or regulation, or if SHEWRITES reasonably believes it is necessary to protect SHEWRITES, its members or the public.
  * Except as described above, we will not disclose your personal information to other third parties unless you have provided consent.

**Special attention to children** ** **

SHEWRITES takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of young people accessing and using our products and services.  SHEWRITES does not specifically collect information about children and believes that children should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information.  SHEWRITES encourages you to participate in and supervise your child’s Internet experience.

The Site and SHEWRITES services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through our Site.

As a matter of policy, SHEWRITES does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from anyone under the age of 13 or allow such persons to access or respond to telephone calls or e-mails from SHEWRITES.

If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any personal information through our Site or otherwise without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

For information on how to protect the privacy and safety of children online, we recommend that you visit the Parents' and Teachers' Guide to Online Privacy and the Consumer portion of the TRUSTe site ([](http://www.truste.org/)[http://www.truste.org](http://www.truste.org/)), which contains information and links to other resources on this subject.  Although SHEWRITES is not affiliated with TRUSTe or any other online privacy oversight program, we do recommend that consumers become familiar with TRUSTe and other online privacy oversight programs and business watch organizations.

**Choices for your Site interactions** ** **

  * You may instruct SHEWRITES to stop sending you certain promotional materials (e.g., email messages, catalogues, notices for products, services, opportunities) by contacting SHEWRITES by email, telephone or through the contact form on the web site.
  * You may choose to view or edit your personal information, which has been stored online, by visiting the “my account” section of the Site.  For the security of your account, you will be required to sign in with your login ID and password.
  * You may contact SHEWRITES to determine the types of personal information that we process and to correct or update your personal information.

**Updating your personal information and privacy preferences**

You have the right to access, correct and delete inaccuracies in your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Registration Information (as defined in the section entitled "Protection Personal Information"), this may be accomplished by logging in to your account on the relevant SHEWRITES website, where you can typically view and make changes to your personal information. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications) by writing to SHEWRITES at:

She Writes, Inc.

60 State Street #3C

Brooklyn, NY 11201-6750

Attn:  Privacy

Please include your name, manual signature, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. No specific form is required to notify SHEWRITES of changes to your address or privacy preferences, but your signature on a written request is required.

Personal information submitted through this Site or in connection with the Products and Services that is not Registration Information is not accessible online. To correct such information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications), you may write to SHEWRITES at:

She Writes, Inc.

60 State Street #3C

Brooklyn, NY 11201-6750

Users may also email: [privacy@shewrites.com](mailto:privacy@shewrites.com) for further information or help in this regard.

In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site or otherwise where you provided your personal information. You may expect a response within 30 days. For information submitted in connection with Products and Services, you may also follow instructions included or referenced within such Product and Services to access, correct or delete inaccuracies in the information.

**Privacy Policy Compliance**

If you feel that SHEWRITES has not complied with the policies outlined in this privacy statement please submit a report to us at [privacy@shewrites.com](mailto:privacy@shewrites.com). Please try to describe the incident, event and nature of the event so that we can move to correct any failures on our part or avoid future oversights.

**How to contact SHEWRITES with questions or comments** ** **

SHEWRITES is happy to answer your questions and listen to your comments.  SHEWRITES offers several options for you to contact us.

**By Email** : services@shewrites.com

**By Fax** : 917-591-8492

**By Mail** : She Writes, Inc.

60 State Street #3C

Brooklyn, NY 11201-6750
